(Penny:)I just love decorating the Christmas tree,
it makes me feel like a little girl again.
(Leonard:)We didn't have a tree
when I was growing up.
(Penny:)-Really? Why not?
-Mm, in my family...
(Leonard:)...holidays weren't so much celebrated,
as studied for their anthropological...
(Leonard:)...and psychological implications
on human society.
(Penny:)Oh, sounds festive.
Did you at least give presents?
Hm, in a way. We presented papers.
(Leonard:)And then broke off into focus groups
and critiqued each other.
(Penny:)Sheldon, what about you?
Did you have a tree?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes.
(Sheldon:)We had a tree, we had a manger...
(Sheldon:)...we had an inflatable Santa Claus
with plastic reindeer on the front lawn.
To make things more jolly, there were
so many blinking lights on the house...
(Sheldon:)...they induced
neighborhood-wide seizures.
I take it you don't wanna
help us trim the tree?
(Sheldon:)I do not. But if you insist on decorating
a spider-infested fire hazard in my home...